Financial domination. Out of all the sexual fetishes in the world, financial domination
is perhaps one of the most glamorous fetishes.
Much like physical forms of BDSM, it's the surrendering of the power that is arousing
for the client. What is it? Financial
domination, or findom for short, is a fetish where women are sent money and
lavished with expensive gifts by men who seemingly want next to nothing in return.
It's all about submitting to the dominant woman and relinquishing control.
A submissive male who fetishises spending money on dominant females, or women in
general, or gives money and gifts without receiving any sexual contact in return.
He is not classed as a sugar daddy because there is no exchange or expectation of
sex in return. Often there is no physical contact of any kind between the findom
and her slave. The slave's motivation for spending is rather the humiliation of spending
money on her. This fetish stems from the male feeling inadequate and like he can't
measure up. Why
financial domination? Low self-esteem. Most subs get into
findom due to low self-esteem. When a submissive is discussing the transfer of money
with his dom, he enters the zone, which is where he is free from all his worries
and becomes aroused. Findom is merely another form of escapism for people who struggle
with everyday life. Inadequacy. Guys who get into findom are often guys who
feel very inadequate. Powerful family. Maybe they
come from a powerful family and feel like they can't live up to their family's expectations
in their subconscious. Being a financial slave is a solution.
These men don't want to have to perform sexually because of how small they feel.
This often becomes an addiction. They get gratification from giving their money away
in order to satisfy women who don't care less about them.
Whatever the reason for these men's inadequacies, at the end of the day, this is
what they want. They get off on sexualising their greatest fears, which are a woman
having power over them and losing all their money.
Put into practice. Blackmail. Ensure there
is a written and signed contract. Know your limits, what you can and can't
do. When it comes to things like blackmail, which a lot of men desire, you need to
make sure there is a written and signed contract.
But I would generally avoid getting too far into blackmail and to stay on the safe
side. The 80-20 rule. 80% of your revenue will come from 20
% of your clients. This is tried and true in business.
This means you will have time wasters or low revenue subs.
Don't run from this. Don't be quick to block subs you judge as broke.
It only takes a few seconds to respond. Take the time to do so.
But with that being said, make sure you spend extra time with those big spenders.
Respond more quickly, take more time to build up conversation or even spend time
just chatting. These type of clients typically favour relationships, so cultivate
it. Declare, don't question. Nervous doms ask a lot of questions.
It shows lack of knowledge or insecurity.
Don't do it. Make sure you demand respect.
There are ways to gather information without asking for it.
When you need to gain information, use declarative sentences.
Compare. Does it make you hard when you tip me?
2. I know how hard it makes you when you send your goddess a huge tip.
In one case, you are giving up power, letting them control the discussion.
When the very thing they are looking for is to give up control.
When using declarative sentences, you make a statement and judge by their reaction
if you should follow that path. There will be times when they do not react well.
If they have their cam open or their sound on, you can tell by their breathing.
If they are just typing, you can tell by how often and how long it takes them to
respond. If they are breathing heavier and clearly stroking, then you state, it will
feel so amazing when I finally log into your email and let all your friends and family
know I own you. If the breathing dies, pivot.
Go back to loss of financial control. If you mention how hard they will be when their
webcam finally goes on so you can watch them and their breathing picks up again,
stay with that. Be ready to adjust but always lead.
Rarely question, control the session and discuss.
Make declarative sentences and react. Some
findom relationships consist of one off payments, whereas others consist of regular
transfers of money. And the more extreme findom relationships will consist
of your sub giving you full control to his bank.
So giving you his passwords for his bank accounts.
And then you will then give him a minimum budget to live off, and you will take the
rest of the money. There are a lot of different names for a findom client.
A couple of examples include PayPig, Human ATM, Cash Slave and Gift Slave.
A findom interaction will be more than just taking his slave's money.
You will taunt him over the phone or on cam.
Whatever he's into, it's best to explore it.
This could be humiliation, cuckold, small penis humiliation.
A lot of the domination tactics are going to help you with your findom client.
But you need to also make sure that whatever money he's giving you that it's going
to have no effect on you. You need to lie to them basically and make them believe
that you live an extravagant life already because this is going to draw him to you.
The more amazing you make your lifestyle seem to him and the more extravagant and
lavish is literally going to make him crumble and come to you every single time.
And with that being said, I'd like to say good luck girls and let us know how you
get on with your findom clients. See ya!